Hello guys, so as [music] you
saw in my previous videos that my Skodavi
caught fire and my car
insurance was with ICICI Lombard [music]
and ICICI LBR rejected my claim saying
that I had after
market fittings installed in it.  When I
asked the name of that accessory [music],
he said that if you have a big issue
then you can file a case in the court.  For that
I also uploaded a video in which
ICICI LBRD publicly gave me a legal threat
that [music] if I do not remove this video
then they can take legal action against me.  I
got a lot of support from you people in that video and I also filed a case in the Lok Adalat
and a lot of comments were coming from you people asking what
happened in that case?  What
was his status after that?  So let me tell you that I had
filed that case in May 2025 and
after that I had two hearings.  One in July
and one in September and
ICICI Lombard did not appear in both the hearings.  I don't know
what the reason was?  Did
n't the notice reach them [music]
or X Wazi region?  So what have we done for that now
?  We spoke to the advocate and got
those notices issued from the Lok Adalat [music].
Now
we will hand over [music] to them by hand at their head office in Jaipur
and
we will courier it to their head office in Mumbai.  We will track it [music] and
I will definitely share with you guys
what its status is
like it gets delivered and my
next yearning is on 12th November 2025.
So hopefully, when I come back after handing over this
and the courier is delivered,
someone will appear on behalf of ICICI Lombard [Music] on November 12 and my hearing will
proceed.  So let us first handover
their notice to ICICI Lo LB.  So this
is the Signature Tower in which the Jaipur office of ICICI Lo LBA
is situated and this
Signature Tower is situated in Tonk Road, Jaipur.
ICICI LB office is situated on the 10th
floor of Signature Tower.
So we have come to the Jaipur head office of ICICI Lombard.
Now let us hand over the notice to them.
Finally we have issued summons to ICICI Lombard.  It has been
handed over and
they have also given it to us with the receipt stamp.
So hopefully, on
November 12, someone will appear on behalf of ICICI Lombard
and the hearing of my case will
proceed.  Apart from that,
our second copy, which is to go to ICICI Lombard
's main head office in Mumbai, is its
summons and this is our entire petition, which
we will courier to ICICI Lombard's Mumbai head office.
Their address
is ICICI Lo LBA General Insurance,
located at Prabha Devi in ​​Mumbai.
These are their complete details. Now we will
pack it and get it couriered. The
pack is ready. Now we will leave
and post it by speed post. There will be a
tracking slip. We will keep tracking it to see
when it reaches them. So,
finally, we have couriered the
notice [music] and petition to ICICI Lombard's Mumbai head office as well. The
vote
[music] was delivered to them on November 3, 2025, as you
can see on the screen. The date when
we handed over the summons to them at the Jaipur head office
was October 8, 2025.
Our next hearing date is
November 12, 2025. So, hopefully, this time ICICI  There will be
someone appearing on Lombard's behalf [music],
our hearing will proceed and I will definitely share with you
what happens in that hearing, what
progress my case makes,
and one thing I
want to tell you again is that my purpose of uploading this video is to
provide correct information to you people, if you people have
also had such an experience [music] then
what are the processes involved in it.
God forbid, if something like this happens to you too, then
what should we do?  I have no motive to
defame any [music] company.
What if the company starts
publicly giving me legal threats that I am
defaming their company?  I don't have any such
motive.
I will definitely update you on what happens on November 12th.  So
guys thanks for staying till the end of the video.  I
hope you enjoy this [music]
video.  If you like it, please like and
comment.  Share this video
with your friends and
subscribe to our channel Explore [Music].
So see you in the next video.
Bye till then.